ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dubinsky, Ryna and Mayor ODwyer at dinner plus other Ryna photos (item no.206) (Box 6, Folder 206)
- Dubinsky, Ryna photos (item no.207) (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Dubinsky, Emma candid (item no.208) (Box 6, Folder 208)
- Dubinsky and Emma on platform at a convention (item no.209) (Box 6, Folder 209)
- Dubinsky, Ryna birthday party, 1948 (item no.210) (Box 6, Folder 210)
- Dubinsky and niece, Charlotte Margolin (Dubinskys niece from Israel), at desk in new office (item no.211) (Box 6, Folder 211)
- Dubinsky, Emma, and Jean, old photo at home (item no.212) (Box 6, Folder 212)
- Danish, Max and the Dubinsky family (old photo) (item no.213) (Box 6, Folder 213)
- Dubinsky and Ryna in office, Ryna holding American Federationalist (item no.214) (Box 6, Folder 214)
- Dubinsky and Emma Dubinsky in formal attire (item no.215) (Box 6, Folder 215)
- Dubinsky, Emma conversing with daughter, Jean (item no.216) (Box 6, Folder 216)
- Woman with baby (item no.217) (Box 6, Folder 217)
- Dubinskys brothers unveiling (item no.218) (Box 6, Folder 218)
- Dubinsky, Brothers keys and book (item no.219) (Box 6, Folder 219)
- Dubinsky, Ryna photos (item no.220) (Box 6, Folder 220)
- Shelly, Jean, Ryna Appleton, and Dubinsky (item no.1) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Dubinsky, Ryna and Sammy, dog in car (item no.2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Dubinsky, Ryna passport photos and others (item no.3) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Dubinsky, Ryna photos (item no.4) (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Dubinsky, Eva, a child in the Dubinsky family portrait (item no.5) (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Dubinsky, Emma and Jean Dubinsky aboard boat, laughing (item no.6) (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Dubinsky, Mr. & Mrs., heads together at dinner (item no.7) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Dubinsky, Wilkie, LaGuardia and others on platform (item no.8) (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Dubinsky, John L. Lewis at convention (item no.9) (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Dubinsky portrait, by Schwartz (item no.10) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Dubinsky in party hat speaking (item no.11) (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Dubinsky, Jimmy (James) Walker in dress suits at dinner (item no.12) (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Dubinsky, Emma Dubinsky, Harry Crone, others in party hats, cutting up at convention party (item no.13) (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Dubinsky kissing his wife (item no.14) (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Dubinsky and niece, Charlotte Margolin (seated on desk) in old office (item no.15) (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Dubinsky and Charles Zimmerman (item no.16) (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Dubinsky and cast of Pins and Needles on stage after performance (item no.17) (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Dubinsky, Mrs. Roosevelt pinning orchids on dress (item no.18) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- David Dubinsky and Rockefeller at dinner (item no.19) (Box 7, Folder 19)
- David Dubinsky and Matthew Woll embracing (item no.20) (Box 7, Folder 20)
- David Dubinsky and Truman on stage speaking (item no.21) (Box 7, Folder 21)
- David Dubinsky and Truman seated in audience (item no.22) (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Antonini Speaking as Dubinsky looks on and Dubinsky speaking as Antonini looks on Hotel Pennsylvania (item no.23) (Box 7, Folder 23)
- David Dubinsky and Professor Schlichter holding check (item no.24) (Box 7, Folder 24)
- David Dubinsky, Jimmy Walker, Israel Feinberg and heads of cloak associations signing contract (item no.25) (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Danish, Max with Dubinsky, Umhey, Alice Donovan, Helen Rooney, Harry Rubenstein, Hannah Haskell, party in the Justice office (item no.26) (Box 7, Folder 26)
- David Dubinsky with sailors and girls seated at table (item no.27) (Box 7, Folder 27)
- David Dubinsky, Hochman, John L. Lewis, Antonini & Nagler (item no.28) (Box 7, Folder 28)
- David Dubinsky, Adolph Held & J. Hochman at dinner (item no.29) (Box 7, Folder 29)
- David Dubinsky and Israel Feinberg holding check (item no.30) (Box 7, Folder 30)
- David Dubinsky greets Reisberg Jr. at dinner (item no.31) (Box 7, Folder 31)
- David Dubinsky and Carrie Snyder, organizer South Jersey (item no.32) (Box 7, Folder 32)
- David Dubinsky, Truman, Garden meeting, 1948 Campaign (item no.33) (Box 7, Folder 33)
- David Dubinsky, Educator & J. Hochman (item no.34) (Box 7, Folder 34)
- David Dubinsky leaving for Europe with Trade Union Delegation, 1936 (item no.35) (Box 7, Folder 35)
- David Dubinsky press conference in new office (item no.36) (Box 7, Folder 36)
- David Dubinsky press conference (item no.37) (Box 7, Folder 37)
- David Dubinsky and Isidore Nagler (item no.38) (Box 7, Folder 38)
- David Dubinsky and General Donovan (item no.39) (Box 7, Folder 39)
- David Dubinsky speaking over WMCA from shop, Red Cross rally (item no.40) (Box 7, Folder 40)
- David Dubinsky and Eleanor Herrick, 1937 convention (item no.41) (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Dubinsky profile, 1945 (item no.42), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- David Dubinsky registering to vote (item no.43), 1945 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Blum, Leon and Dubinsky in London (item no.44) (Box 7, Folder 44)
- David Dubinsky, George Meany, William Green, William ODwyer at AFL meeting in Garden to veto Taft-Hartley Bill, 5/4/47 & Veto Slave Labor Bill sign (item no.45), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  May 4th
- Dubinsky, Green and ODwyer handshake at AFL meeting (item no.46) (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Dubinsky speaking at AFL meeting to veto Labor Bill (item no.47) (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Dubinsky, Rose Zimmerman & Antonini at Joint Board dinner (item no.48) (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Scholarship Committee meeting, 6/7/63 (item no.49), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  June 7th
- Wilkie, Wendell and Dubinsky conferring in Wilkies office (item no.50) (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Walker, James with Dubinsky, George Jessel, and a judge (item no.51) (Box 7, Folder 51)
- LaGuardia and Dubinsky on tour of shop during Red Cross Rally (item no.52) (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Haskel, Hannah parties. 6/12-14/63. (item no.53), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  June 12th-14th
- Thomas, Norman portrait (item no.54) (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Danish, Max Danish family (item no.55) (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Woll, Matthew on retrum from ICFTU Conference in London on Queen Elizabeth with Dubinsky, Mrs. Dubinsky, and Mrs. Woll, 12/26/49 (item no.56), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  December 26th
- Dubinsky speaking at International Ladies Garment meeting for Defense Bonds campaign (item no.57) (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Dubinsky shaking hands with member of audience from platform after speaking (item no.58) (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Dubinsky, Hochman, Zimmerman press conference, old office (item no.59) (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Dubinsky speaking at dinner (color photos) (item no.60) (Box 7, Folder 60)
  color photos
- Zimmerman, Charles seated at dinner as Hochman speaks (color photo) (item no.61) (Box 7, Folder 61)
  color photo
- Dubinsky, hat and cigar amidst crowd of people with hands outstretched towards him for Garden tickets, 1948 political rally (item no.62) (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Dubinsky, Robert Wagner Sr., Eleanor Herrick, Lehman & Alex Rose (item no.63) (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Dubinsky is presented with Delft Plaque by Dutch Delegation (item no.64) (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Dubinsky, William Green shaking hands at Pins and Needles (item no.65) (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Green, William, Dubinsky handshake Pins and Needles (item no.66) (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Dubinsky shakes hands with Madame Secretary, Frances Perkins (NRA) (item no.67) (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Counts, George S. with Dubinsky, Truman & Alex Rose with Liberal Party election poster (item no.68) (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Dubinsky, Oscar Ewing, Truman, James Mead, Lehman (item no.69) (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Dubinsky signing autographs for workers (item no.70) (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Dubinsky, Sidney Hillman & Lehman (item no.71) (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Dubinsky, Mrs. Roosevelt in lobby of theatre (Pins and Needles) (item no.72) (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Dubinsky, Sidney Hillman, and Eleanor Herrick (item no.73) (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Dubinsky (laughing) with Harry Hopkins (item no.74) (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Dubinsky and Mrs. Salvatore Ninfo (item no.75) (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Dubinsky at Vatican (item no.76) (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Dubinsky factory visit in Italy (item no.77) (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Antonini, Dubinsky, Emma Dubinsky, group shot on Italian visit (item no.78) (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Dubinsky, Sidney Hillman Grand Central Station- To Trains (item no.79) (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Dubinsky and Rose Zimmerman (item no.80) (Box 7, Folder 80)
- Dubinsky with European visitors (Italian) (item no.81) (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Dubinsky, Jean in evening clothes clapping hands (item no.82) (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Dubinsky, Robert Sherwood, Henry Morgenthau, Mrs. Roosevelt; Humphreys Dinner, 1948 (item no.83) (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Antonini, Gelo, Dubinsky, Lehman, and Elinore Herrick (item no.84) (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Chevenalls and Dubinsky, handshake at dinner (item no.85) (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Dubinsky receives plaque from English Trade Union Delegation (item no.86) (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Dubinsky receives Treasury Department Citation from representative of department (item no.87) (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Dubinsky presenting check; looking on are Antonini, Feinberg & Hochman (item no.88) (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Dubinsky and Wolchek speak at English War picture display (item no.89) (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Dubinsky, Nathan Margolis, Abraham Snyder, Rubin Zuckerman, Hochman, and Nagler (item no.90) (Box 7, Folder 90)
- Dubinsky, Newbold, Morris, and Harry Uviller at Russian War Relief clothing collection (item no.91) (Box 7, Folder 91)
- Dubinsky, Matthew Woll, & Charles Zimmerman (informal photo) (item no.92) (Box 7, Folder 92)
- Dubinsky poses with workers delegation in office, candid (item no.93) (Box 7, Folder 93)
- Dubinsky with Spanish Labor Leader in office (item no.94) (Box 7, Folder 94)
- Dubinsky at dedication of new Needle Trades High School building (speaking) (item no.95) (Box 7, Folder 95)
- Reissberg, Sadie candid (item no.96) (Box 7, Folder 96)
- Carey, James and William Green, candid (item no.97) (Box 7, Folder 97)
- Dubinsky with North East Department staff, 1935, accepting gift scroll (item no.98) (Box 7, Folder 98)
- Dubinsky accepting welfare contributions from Local 102 (item no.99) (Box 7, Folder 99)
- Dubinsky presenting check to Red Cross 1944 (item no.100) (Box 7, Folder 100)
- Dubinsky with McGoldrick at Local painting exhibit (item no.101) (Box 7, Folder 101)
- Berry, George of AFL and Dubinsky shaking hands (item no.102) (Box 7, Folder 102)
- Dubinsky, members of Local 99 present check to Red Cross (item no.103) (Box 7, Folder 103)
- Dubinsky, Miscellaneous (item no.104) (Box 7, Folder 104)
- Dubinsky, Miscellaneous (item no.105) (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Dubinsky, Miscellaneous (item no.106) (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Hochman candid (item no.107) (Box 7, Folder 107)
- Baroff, Abraham portrait (item no.108) (Box 7, Folder 108)
- Braff, Bernard portrait (item no.109) (Box 7, Folder 109)
- Brandeis, Justice Louis Brandeis portrait (item no.110) (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Antonini Honored at City Hall, 9/5/63 (item no.111), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  September 5th
- London, Meyer portrait (item no.112) (Box 7, Folder 112)
- Antonini, Weekend at Unity House, 9/7/63 (item no.113), 1963 (Box 7, Folder 113)
- McCauley, James portrait (item no.114) (Box 7, Folder 114)
- Schlesinger, Benjamin portraits, (item no.115) (Box 7, Folder 115)
- Sigman, M. portraits (item no.116) (Box 7, Folder 116)
- Local 89 charter (item no.117) (Box 7, Folder 117)
- First International Ladies Garment Workers Union Charter of Affiliation with AFL, 1900 (item no.118) (Box 7, Folder 118)
- Protocol of Peace in the Dress & Waist Industry, top half of pamphlet cover (item no.119) (Box 7, Folder 119)
- Membership card, Ladies Waistmakers Union, New York and temporary Working Card, Local 25, during General Strike, 1921, (item no.120) (Box 7, Folder 120)
- Checks to Sanitariums from Sick and TB Benefit Fund Local 22 (item no.121) (Box 7, Folder 121)
- Picture of charters granted to Locals by International Ladies Garment Workers Union (item no.122) (Box 7, Folder 122)
- NRA Emblem (item no.123) (Box 7, Folder 123)
- International Ladies Garment Constitution and Receipt Book, Loc. 25, 1913, Missing (item no.124) (Box 7, Folder 124)
- International Ladies Garment Constitution and Receipt Book, Loc. 9, 1917 (item no.125) (Box 7, Folder 125)
- Passport from Europe (item no.126) (Box 7, Folder 126)
- Letterhead of Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers Union, Morris Sigman, Mgr. (item no.127) (Box 7, Folder 127)
- Dedication on plaque on honor of Sigman and Schlesinger (item no.128) (Box 7, Folder 128)
- Inscribed watch given to Philip KaPlowitz by Morris Hillquit for his services, 1915 (item no.129) (Box 7, Folder 129)
- Dubinsky, Jean and Korean Delegate Chun Chin Han shaking hands and looking at Life Magazine (item no.130) (Box 7, Folder 130)
- Han, Chun Chin (Delegate from Korea to World Labor Conference) and Yu Ki Tai (another delegate) (item no.131) (Box 7, Folder 131)
  Looking at photo of Einstein and Pins and Needles cast on wall in International Ladies Garment Workers Union headquarters
- Women Cutters, 1920 (item no.132) (Box 7, Folder 132)
- Print of Tailor Shop, 1568 (item no.133) (Box 7, Folder 133)
- Sweatshop, 1900, Drawing (item no.134) (Box 7, Folder 134)
- Men sewing on machines, 1914 (item no.135) (Box 7, Folder 135)
- Men sewing on machines, 1925 (item no.136) (Box 7, Folder 136)
- Men sewing on machines, 1928 (item no.137) (Box 7, Folder 137)
- Pressers, 1930 (item no.138) (Box 7, Folder 138)
- Pressers, 1910 (item no.139) (Box 7, Folder 139)
- Pressers working in attic, 1912 (item no.140) (Box 7, Folder 140)
- Sweatshop, 1913 (item no.141) (Box 7, Folder 141)
- Men Hand finishing garments, 1930 (item no.142) (Box 7, Folder 142)
- Sweatshop, 1900, children working (item no.143) (Box 7, Folder 143)
- Women singer, sewing on machine, footwork, (drawing) (item no.144) (Box 7, Folder 144)
  drawing
- Old Time Cloak shop, 1910 (item no.145) (Box 7, Folder 145)
- Woman working at old time Howe sewing machine (item no.146) (Box 7, Folder 146)
- Old Time factory, drawing (item no.147) (Box 7, Folder 147)
- A Traveling Tailor measuring a womans waist, (drawing) (item no.148) (Box 7, Folder 148)
- Tailor Shop, 1300 drawing (item no.149) (Box 7, Folder 149)
- Interior of Home used for homework, shows poor, unsanitary working conditions and dangerous conditions (item no.150) (Box 7, Folder 150)
- People working on artificial flowers in home, 1935 (item no.151) (Box 7, Folder 151)
- Women working on knitgoods at home, 1935 (item no.152) (Box 7, Folder 152)
- Early drawing of family working on garments at home (item no.153) (Box 7, Folder 153)
- Interior of home used as shop showing violations, 1935 (item no.154) (Box 7, Folder 154)
- Homes of Garment Workers in San Antonio, Texas showing homework and poor conditions (item no.155) (Box 7, Folder 155)
  (4 negatives)
- Alleyway of factories, 1928 sweatshop alley (item no.156) (Box 7, Folder 156)
- Orchard Street, early scene (item no.157) (Box 7, Folder 157)
- Historical Election, July 31, 1915, New York Garment Center strike vote, Left to Right: M. Israelson, A. Goldberg, M. Boilenson, Sam Robertson, and Sam Benenson (item no.158) (Box 7, Folder 158)
  July 31st
- Striking East Side Garment Workers dancing (item no.159) (Box 7, Folder 159)
- Acting Govenor of New York Lehman checks Cloak strike. Ingersoll, Dubinsky, and others. (item no.160) (Box 7, Folder 160)
- Charles Zimmerman, Tom Dewey, Julius Hochman, Charney B. Vladeck on stage at a meeting. (item no.161) (Box 7, Folder 161)
- Charney B. Vladeck and Polish Delegate at International Ladies Garment convention. (item no.162) (Box 7, Folder 162)
- Local 10 installation of officers, 1935. (item no.163) (Box 7, Folder 163)
- Early delegation to Washington (item no.164) (Box 7, Folder 164)
  David Dubinsky, William Green, John L. Lewis, Labor Secretary Frances Perkins, and others
- May 1927, Cleveland. Kreindler, Benjamin Kaplan, and others. (item no.165) (Box 7, Folder 165)
- Morris Sigman and LaGuardia conversing at outdoor meeting Sept. 20, 1926 (item no.166) (Box 7, Folder 166)
  September 20th
- Old time Cloakmakers Executive Board (item no.167) (Box 7, Folder 167)
- Early union committee. Albany. (item no.168), 1929 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  Seated: Ben Schlesinger, Morris Hoff, Gov. Roosevelt, and Isadore Grossman. Standing: Guerney, Cross (Sec. to Roosevelt), Lt. Gov. Lehman, and Joseph Schwartz.
- Sigman, Dubinsky, Nagler, on beach boardwalk (item no.169) (Box 7, Folder 169)
- NRA Alfred W. Lasher, Grover Whalen and Dubinsky (item no.170), 1933 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  August 18th
- Early Union officials including Gingold (item no.171) (Box 7, Folder 171)
- Funeral Procession for Meyer London (item no.172) (Box 7, Folder 172)
- Union meeting, 1910 Beethoven Hall (item no.173) (Box 7, Folder 173)
- Workers gather and talk on 35th Street between 7th and 8th Avenues (Garment Center) (item no.174) (Box 7, Folder 174)
- Early Executive Board (item no.175) (Box 7, Folder 175)
  Includes President Schlesinger, Baroff, Dubinsky, Antonini, Hochman, and others
- Agreement signing, Dubinsky, Umhey, and others 7/29/32 (item no.176), 1932 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  July 29th
- Northeast Department, 1937 (item no.177) (Box 7, Folder 177)
- Buttons (item no.178), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 178)
- Stretcher laying out material to be cut (item no.179) (Box 7, Folder 179)
  (2 negatives)(P)
- Cutter working on batch of material with machine (item no.180) (Box 7, Folder 180)
  (P)
- Closeup of cutter working with machine (item no.181) (Box 7, Folder 181)
- Long view of interior of cutting shop (item no.182) (Box 7, Folder 182)
- Cutters at work with machine (item no.183) (Box 7, Folder 183)
- Cutters at work with machine (item no.187) (Box 7, Folder 184)
- Lone cutter at work, close-ups (item no.188) (Box 7, Folder 185)
- LaGuardia watching cutter at work (item no.189) (Box 7, Folder 186)
- Cutters working in underwear during heat spell (item no.190) (Box 7, Folder 187)
- 2 stretchers laying out material (item no.191) (Box 7, Folder 188)
- Cutter at work lying across table to cut the mater (item no.192) (Box 7, Folder 189)
- Cutting shop at work (item no.193) (Box 7, Folder 190)
- Cutter working with hand shears Plus Notching (item no.194) (Box 7, Folder 191)
- 3 cutters working on batch of material (item no.194) (Box 7, Folder 192)
  (N)
- Joe Kessler looks on as worker cements raincoat while another trims bottom with shears (item no.195) (Box 7, Folder 193)
- Cutter sloping material (item no.196) (Box 7, Folder 194)
- Mannequins (item no.197) (Box 7, Folder 195)
- Woman draping unfinished blouse on form (item no.198) (Box 7, Folder 196)
- Man buttoning finished jacket on form (item no.199) (Box 7, Folder 197)
- Man fitting basted sample jacket on form (item no.200) (Box 7, Folder 198)
- Man fitting womans coat, draping sleeves on form (item no.201) (Box 7, Folder 199)
- Sample maker working on dress on form (item no.202) (Box 7, Folder 200)
- Woman sample maker draping dress on form (item no.203) (Box 7, Folder 201)
- Man altering hem on womans coat (item no.204) (Box 7, Folder 202)
- Woman samplemaker draping jacket on form (item no.205) (Box 7, Folder 203)
- Fitting coats on models (item no.206) (Box 7, Folder 204)
- Man measuring first part of sample on form and girl (item no.207) (Box 7, Folder 205)
- Woman fitting white collar to dress worn by another woman (item no.208) (Box 7, Folder 206)
- Woman samplemaker working on louse on form (item no.209) (Box 7, Folder 207)
- Woman fitting dress to form (item no.210) (Box 7, Folder 208)
- Woman examining slips on hangers (item no.211) (Box 7, Folder 209)
- Woman examining childrens coats (item no.212) (Box 7, Folder 210)
- Woman cleaning up childrens coats (item no.213) (Box 7, Folder 211)
- Girl cleaning up middie blouses (item no.214) (Box 7, Folder 212)
- Girls examining shirts and girl examining childrens dressery (item no.215) (Box 7, Folder 213)
- Girl holding examined and cleaned blouse in front of her (item no.216) (Box 7, Folder 214)
- Women examining racks of dresses (item no.217) (Box 7, Folder 215)
- Women examining dresses on forms (item no.218) (Box 7, Folder 216)
- Women examining racks of negligees (item no.219) (Box 7, Folder 217)
- Man examining coat on form (item no.220) (Box 7, Folder 218)
- Girl examining raincoats (item no.221) (Box 7, Folder 219)
- Womans hands sewing button on coat (item no.222) (Box 7, Folder 220)
- Woman hand finishing gown on form (item no.223) (Box 7, Folder 221)
- Woman hand finishing raincoats (item no.224) (Box 7, Folder 222)
- Three women hand finishing robes (item no.225) (Box 7, Folder 223)
- Two women finishing collars (item no.226) (Box 7, Folder 224)
- Closeup of girl hand finishing garment at table (item no.227) (Box 7, Folder 225)
- Men hand finishing womens coats (item no.228) (Box 7, Folder 226)
- Elderly man and woman finishing coat linings (item no.229) (Box 7, Folder 227)
- Woman working on trimmings for garments (item no.230) (Box 7, Folder 228)
- Woman working at pinking machine with dust mask on face (item no.231) (Box 7, Folder 229)
- Elderly man with beard finishing coat (item no.232) (Box 7, Folder 230)
  Missing
- Elderly man working on jacket with shears (item no.233) (Box 7, Folder 231)
- Women sewing buttons on finished garments (item no.234) (Box 7, Folder 232)
- Room of finishers at work in shop, 5 women, 1 man (item no.235) (Box 7, Folder 233)
- Finishers at work in shop, supervisor looking on (item no.236) (Box 7, Folder 234)
- Women at table hand finishing dresses (item no.237) (Box 7, Folder 235)
  (P and 4 Negatives)
- Two girls working on zippers of evening gowns (item no.238) (Box 7, Folder 236)
- Two men hand finishing garments at table (item no.239) (Box 7, Folder 237)
- Women hand finishing garments (item no.240) (Box 7, Folder 238)
  (P and 3 negactives)
- Woman and elderly man at work at table (item no.241) (Box 7, Folder 239)
- Close up, elderly man with beard using shears on jacket, pictorial, good (P) (item no.242) (Box 7, Folder 240)
- Nathan, Robert portrait at WFDR mike (item no.243) (Box 7, Folder 241)
- Allen, Will, portrat at WFDR mike (item no.244) (Box 7, Folder 242)
- Herling, J. portrait at WFDR mike (item no.1) (Box 7, Folder 243)
- Clapper, Mrs. Raymond portrait at WFDR mike (item no.2) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Childs, Marquis portrait at WFDR mike (item no.3) (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Woman removing stains and dirt from finished garments (item no.4) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Girls hand finishing garments (war work) (item no.5) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Man cements raincoat (cementing process) (item no.6) (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Women making covered buttons on machine (item no.7) (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Plastic work, Local 132 girls working (item no.8) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Belt maker at work (item no.9) (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Girl working on hook and eye machine (P) (item no.10) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Man working at machine covering belt buckles (P) (item no.11) (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Man making Buckle covers by hand (P) (item no.12) (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Belt maker stretching belts and other cutting belts on machine (chopper) (P) (item no.13) (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Man spraying with air gun, plastic shop (P)-no protection masks (item no.14) (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Girls making artificial flowers by hand (P) (item no.15) (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Man cutting artificial flowers by machine (P) (item no.16) (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Artificial Flower Display (item no.17) (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Women plastic workers on drill presses (item no.18) (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Plastic worker on cutting machine (P) (item no.19) (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Plastic worker on lathe (P) (item no.20) (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Women putting together artificial flowers (P) (item no.21) (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Women working on button covering machine (P) (item no.22) (Box 8, Folder 21)